{
  "N5": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "How old ___ you?",
      "answers": 
        [
          "are",
          "is",
          "do",
          "does"
        ],
      "correct": "89d07805e842faba2ae8c2584e06c50b"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "What ___ your name?",
      "answers": 
        [
          "do", 
          "are", 
          "is", 
          "does"
        ],
      "correct": "2c09dac7916eef0e8f72f1af5ce4e416"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "Where ___ you from?",
      "answers": 
        [
          "does",
          "do",
          "is",
          "are"
        ],
      "correct": "bf9b5686ef49931d1f81a9426a5f7de7"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "How ___ you use a public bus?",
      "answers": 
        [
          "does",
          "is",
          "do",
          "did"
        ],
      "correct": "4d4dec4dc14b468c35e460947757c178"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "What time ___ it?",
      "answers": 
        [
          "is",
          "dose",
          "did",
          "do"
        ],
      "correct": "21abffb833335edcc6b6e02afa2a17b7"
    }
  ],
  "N4": [
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "What subject ___ you like?",
      "answers": 
        [
          "are",
          "do",
          "did",
          "is"
        ],
      "correct": "5810b2fb0cd6ef028267892461585def"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "How many books ___ there?",
      "answers": 
        [
          "do",
          "are",
          "is",
          "did"
        ],
      "correct": "860588ba5aaaa096c3b085a99fd6c171"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "Where ___ she work?",
      "answers": 
        [
          "did",
          "is",
          "are",
          "does"
        ],
      "correct": "67bedd7e7774c2e2604bc96c225d4b46"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "What time ___ she go to school?",
      "answers": 
        [
          "are",
          "does",
          "is",
          "do"
        ],
      "correct": "471641e74b03fee9caff77125cef6bdf"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "What animal ___ that?",
      "answers": 
        [
          "is",
          "do",
          "did",
          "does"
        ],
      "correct": "6ad229318eaf2552a2796e223f4887c6"
    }
  ]
}